

Mr Mark

Hotel Manager - Management Admin Bachelor

Connect

♠ Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

♠ Message

• • •

Mr Mark · 3rd

Hotel Manager - Management Admin Bachelor

Vietnam · 105 connections · Contact info

Vietnam Hospitality

Business Administration Univercity

People and pages related to Mr

See all



>



Hotel Jobs | JobKing.org

Page • Staffing & Recruiting

Follow



Hospitality Information & Jobs Vacancies

Page • Hospitality 327,769 followers

Follow



Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas

Page • Hospitality 145,643 followers

Follow

About

I am a simple person, friendly!

My aim just keep trying my best to contribute the travel environment in Vietnam and sharing acknowledgment as experience to all Vietnamese citizen!

... see more

Activity

106 followers

Posts Mr created, shared, or commented on in the last 90 days are displayed here.

See all activity

Experience

Vietnam Hospitality

11 yrs 8 mos

Hotel Manager

Feb 2013 – Present

· 8 yrs 3 mos

Hanoi, Vietnam

Manage all daily hotel activities, meeting guests. Make sure the hotel's operation run smoothly.

Hotel General Manager

Sep 2009 – Present

· 11 yrs 8 mos

Hanoi, Vietnam

Daily sales, marketing activities and meeting guests to make sure they get what they need.

Hotel General Manager

Rosaliza Hotel

Apr 2008 – Aug 2009

· 1 yr 5 mos

15 Tran Quoc Toan St, Hoan Kiem Dist, Hanoi, Vietnam

Manage daily activities in hotel: Operation, sales, manpower, services, revenue, cost control and maintenance.

Education

Business Administration Univercity

Bachelor's degree, Business, Management, Marketing, and Related Support Services 2009-2013

Skills & endorsements

Management

Hotel Management

Microsoft Office

Industry Knowledge

Project Management

Hospitality Management

Revenue Analysis Pre-opening Food & Beverage **Event Management** Interpersonal Skills **Customer Service** Other Skills 📵 **Hospitality Industry** Marketing and sales, business management, communication. Show less ^ Interests Arianna Huffington in Founder and CEO at Thrive Global

9,802,366 followers



Co-chair, Bill & Melinda Gates Foundation 32,632,203 followers

Hotel Brokers International

3,438 followers

#HBI

Deepak Chopra MD (official) in Founder at Deepak Chopra LLC



6,774,659 followers

Japan International Cooperation Agency (JICA)

52,895 followers



Richard Branson in



Founder at Virgin Group 18,588,076 followers

People also viewed



Stephen O'Grady •3rd

Managing Director at Crosskeys Hospitality Solutions

Connect



venkateshwarlu mukkidi •3rd+

Room Service Waiter at Habtoor Grand Resort, Autograph Collection

Connect



Nazir Khan •3rd+

Finance / Hospitality

Connect

Lea Ruhimbaccus •3rd+ Executive Housekeeper at Waldorf Astoria The Palm Connect

Victoria Taylor •3rd+ 📊

Senior Editor, Community at LinkedIn News

+ Follow

∨Show more

People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Hien Tran

IT Recruitment consultant

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

	Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software		
	Connect		
•			
	Nguyen Dinh Dat		
	Frontend Angular Developer		
	Connect		
	✓Show more		
	Due learn what hiring managers leak for in anguers to ton interview questions		
	Duc, learn what hiring managers look for in answers to top interview questions		
	Teil me about a time you had to persuade someone.		
	Why should we hire you?		
	Tell me about a time you failed or made a mistake.		
	See all questions		

Linked <mark>in</mark>	
About	
Accessibility	
Talent Solutions	
Community Guidelines	
Careers	
Marketing Solutions	
Privacy & Terms ✓	
Ad Choices	
Advertising	
Sales Solutions	
Mobile Control of the	
Small Business	
Safety Center	
Questions? Visit our Help Center.	
Manage your account and privacy Go to your Settings.	
Select Language	
(Arabic) العربية	
inkedIn Corporation © 2021	
	S

